Undergraduate Alumni Records, 18th Century 1748-1799: Preliminary Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
Undergraduate Alumni Records, 18th Century
1748-1799
AC104
Princeton University. Library. Dept. of Rare Books and Special Collections. Seeley G. Mudd Manuscript Library. Princeton University Archives. 65 Olden Street Princeton, New Jersey 08540 USA
1382 files
Princeton University.
Consists of personal files of former undergraduate students of Princeton University. Information in each file varies greatly but can include the names of relatives, notable achievements and news items, address updates, and obituaries.
The College of New Jersey was initially chartered in 1746. The first classes were held in Elizabeth, New Jersey, in the parsonage of the president, the Reverend Jonathan Dickinson. Upon his death, the College moved to Newark, New Jersey, and was headed by the Reverend Aaron Burr, Sr. Since 1756, the College has been located in Princeton, New Jersey. For the first fifty years, nearly all College operations took place within Nassau Hall. Fires, fundraising difficulties, low student enrollment, and the Civil War challenged the vitality of the College in the early and middle nineteenth century, but the College grew vigorously under the leadership of President James McCosh, and it was renamed Princeton University in 1896. The Graduate School was established in 1900, although a limited graduate program had existed since the 1870s. Princeton enthusiastically supported the country (living up to its informal motto, "Princeton in the Nation’s Service") during the First and Second World Wars, offering the expertise of faculty and campus space for training, as well as facilitating the early graduation of students so they could enlist. The post-World War II years brought dramatic changes to Princeton. The size and strength of the University’s facilities and academic programs—especially for the applied sciences and public policy—were increased dramatically. Under President Robert Goheen, Princeton began to admit minority students in greater numbers in the 1960s and admitted women undergraduates in 1969. Today, Princeton is widely regarded as one of the top universities in the world.
Consists of personal files of former undergraduate students of Princeton University. Information in each file varies greatly but can include the names of relatives, notable achievements and news items, address updates, and obituaries.
The collection consists of four series: Series 1 contains files from 1748 to 1799; and Series 2 contains files from 1800 to 1899; Series 3 contains files from 1900 to 1920; and Series 4 contains files with unknown dates.
The collection is open for research use.
Series 2 is available at Alumni Files, 1748-1920: Series 2.
Series 3 is available at Alumni Files, 1748-1920: Series 3.
Series 4 is available at Alumni Files, 1748-1920: Series 4.
A searchable index of undergraduate alumni files is also available: Undergraduate Alumni Database, 1748-1920.
Princeton University. -- Alumni and alumnae.; Princeton University. Students.; College students -- New Jersey -- Princeton.; Princeton University
- Series 1: Alumni Files, 1748-1799; 1382 files
  Series 1 contains files from students in the classes of 1748-1799.
  The files are arranged first by class year and then alphabetically by last name.
  - Ayres, Enos, 1748; portion of 1 box Contains oversize material. (Box 1)
  - Chestnut, Benjamin, 1748; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 1)
  - Henry, Hugh, 1748; portion of 1 box (Box 1)
  - Read, Israel, 1748; portion of 1 box (Box 1)
  - Stockton, Richard, 1748; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. Contains oversize material. (Box 1)
  - Thane, Daniel, 1748; portion of 1 box (Box 1)
  - Brown, John, 1749; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 1)
  - Burnet, William, 1749; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. Contains oversize material. (Box 1)
  - Hoge, John, 1749; portion of 1 box (Box 1)
  - Kennedy, Thomas, 1749; portion of 1 box (Box 1)
  - Moffat, John, 1749; portion of 1 box (Box 1)
  - Todd, John, 1749; portion of 1 box (Box 2)
  - Whittlesey, Eliezer, 1749; portion of 1 box (Box 2)
  - Bay, Hugh, 1750; portion of 1 box (Box 2)
  - Beard, James, 1750; portion of 1 box (Box 2)
  - Clinton, Alexander, 1750; portion of 1 box (Box 2)
  - Farrand, Daniel, 1750; portion of 1 box (Box 2)
  - Frelinghuysen, Jacobus, 1750; portion of 1 box (Box 2)
  - Mitchell, Simeon, 1750; portion of 1 box (Box 2)
  - Badger, Jonathan, 1751; portion of 1 box (Box 2)
  - Clark, Samuel, 1751; portion of 1 box (Box 2)
  - Gordon, Alexander, 1751; portion of 1 box (Box 2)
  - Henry, Robert, 1751; portion of 1 box (Box 2)
  - MacClintock, Samuel, 1751; portion of 1 box (Box 2)
  - Martin, Henry, 1751; portion of 1 box (Box 2)
  - Prime, Benjamin Youngs, 1751; portion of 1 box (Box 2)
  - Ross, Robert, 1751; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 2)
  - Scudder, Nathaniel, 1751; portion of 1 box (Box 2)
  - Thurston, David, 1751; portion of 1 box (Box 2)
  - Clinton, Charles, 1752; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Duffield, George, 1752; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 2)
  - Halsey, Jeremiah, 1752; portion of 1 box (Box 2)
  - Livermore, Samuel, 1752; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 2)
  - Low, Cornelius, 1752; portion of 1 box (Box 2)
  - Whitaker, Nathaniel, 1752; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 3)
  - Wright, John, 1752; portion of 1 box (Box 3)
  - Browne, Daniel Isaac, 1753; portion of 1 box (Box 3)
  - Canfield, Israel, 1753; portion of 1 box (Box 3)
  - Harris, John, 1753; portion of 1 box (Box 3)
  - Harris, Robert, 1753; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 3)
  - Houston, John, 1753; portion of 1 box (Box 3)
  - Jamison, David, 1753; portion of 1 box (Box 3)
  - McAden, Hugh, 1753; portion of 1 box (Box 3)
  - McKesson, John, 1753; portion of 1 box (Box 3)
  - Ogden, Lewis, 1753; portion of 1 box (Box 3)
  - Potter, Nathaniel, 1753; portion of 1 box (Box 3)
  - Sherman, Nathaniel, 1753; portion of 1 box (Box 3)
  - Shippen, Joseph Jr., 1753; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 3)
  - Williams, Elijah, 1753; portion of 1 box (Box 3)
  - Woodruff, Benjamin, 1753; portion of 1 box (Box 3)
  - Woodruff, Joseph, 1753; portion of 1 box (Box 3)
  - Barrett, Moses, 1754; portion of 1 box (Box 3)
  - Chapman, Benjamin, 1754; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Chapman, Benjamin, 1754; portion of 1 box (Box 3)
  - Ewing, John, 1754; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 3)
  - Hait, Benjamin, 1754; portion of 1 box (Box 4)
  - Horton, Ezra, 1754; portion of 1 box (Box 4)
  - Kennedy, Samuel, 1754; portion of 1 box (Box 4)
  - Knox, Hugh, 1754; portion of 1 box Contains oversize material. (Box 4)
  - Mathews, David, 1754; portion of 1 box (Box 4)
  - Odell, Jonathan, 1754; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. Contains oversize material. (Box 4)
  - Osborn, Sylvanus, 1754; portion of 1 box (Box 4)
  - Purviance, David, 1754; portion of 1 box (Box 4)
  - Ramsay, William, 1754; portion of 1 box (Box 4)
  - Reeve, James, 1754; portion of 1 box (Box 4)
  - Roots, Benajah, 1754; portion of 1 box (Box 4)
  - Sherman, Josiah, 1754; portion of 1 box (Box 4)
  - Shippen, William Jr., 1754; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 4)
  - Smith, Thomas, 1754; portion of 1 box (Box 4)
  - Thomson, William, 1754; portion of 1 box (Box 4)
  - Wadham[s], Noah, 1754; portion of 1 box (Box 4)
  - Baldwin, Jonathan, 1755; portion of 1 box (Box 4)
  - Bradner, Benoni, 1755; portion of 1 box (Box 4)
  - Burr, Thaddeus, 1755; portion of 1 box (Box 4)
  - Case, Wheeler, 1755; portion of 1 box (Box 5)
  - Conklin, Benjamin, 1755; portion of 1 box (Box 5)
  - Crawford, William, 1755; portion of 1 box (Box 5)
  - Hanna, John, 1755; portion of 1 box (Box 5)
  - Laydekker, Gerhardus, 1755; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 5)
  - Montgomery, John, 1755; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Montgomery, Joseph, 1755; portion of 1 box (Box 5)
  - Smith, Isaac, 1755; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 5)
  - Stratton, Smith, 1755; portion of 1 box (Box 5)
  - Townsend, Isaac, 1755; portion of 1 box (Box 5)
  - Camp, Stephen, 1756; portion of 1 box (Box 5)
  - Hull, David, 1756; portion of 1 box (Box 5)
  - Livermore, Isaac, 1756; portion of 1 box (Box 5)
  - Livermore, William, 1756; portion of 1 box (Box 5)
  - Martin, Alexander, 1756; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 5)
  - Mills, William, 1756; portion of 1 box (Box 5)
  - Ogden, Josiah, 1756; portion of 1 box (Box 5)
  - Peck, Joseph, 1756; portion of 1 box (Box 5)
  - Riker, John Berrien, 1756; portion of 1 box (Box 5)
  - Roe, Azel, 1756; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 5)
  - Root, Jesse, 1756; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 5)
  - Smith, Jeffrey, 1756; portion of 1 box (Box 5)
  - Baldwin, Moses, 1757; portion of 1 box (Box 5)
  - Barnum, Caleb, 1757; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 5)
  - Bayard, Nicholos, 1757; portion of 1 box (Box 5)
  - Benedict, Noah, 1757; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 6)
  - Boyd, John, 1757; portion of 1 box (Box 6)
  - Browne, William Burnet, 1757; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Brush, Abner, 1757; portion of 1 box (Box 6)
  - Curtis, Caleb, 1757; portion of 1 box (Box 6)
  - Edwards, Timothy, 1757; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 6)
  - Faneuil, Peter, 1757; portion of 1 box (Box 6)
  - Gregory, Elnathan, 1757; portion of 1 box (Box 6)
  - Hun, Thomas, 1757; portion of 1 box (Box 6)
  - Kirkpatrick, William, 1757; portion of 1 box (Box 6)
  - Low, Nicholas, 1757; portion of 1 box (Box 6)
  - MacWhorter, Alexander, 1757; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 6)
  - Murray, ?, 1757; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Murray, unknown, 1757; portion of 1 box (Box 6)
  - Parkhurst, Samuel, 1757; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. Contains oversize material. (Box 6)
  - Reed, Joseph, 1757; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. Contains oversize material. (Box 6)
  - Sayre, Stephen, 1757; portion of 1 box (Box 6)
  - Smith, David, 1757; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 6)
  - Smith, James, 1757; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 6)
  - Strain, John, 1757; portion of 1 box (Box 7)
  - Taylor, Samuel, 1757; portion of 1 box (Box 7)
  - Treat, Joseph, 1757; portion of 1 box (Box 7)
  - Wells, Abner, 1757; portion of 1 box (Box 7)
  - Wells, Henry, 1757; portion of 1 box (Box 7)
  - Borkuloe, John, 1758; portion of 1 box (Box 7)
  - Douw, Peter Winne, 1758; portion of 1 box (Box 7)
  - Hanna, William, 1758; portion of 1 box (Box 7)
  - Johnston, John, 1758; portion of 1 box (Box 7)
  - Ker, Jacob, 1758; portion of 1 box (Box 7)
  - Livingston, Peter Robert, 1758; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 7)
  - Livingston, Philip Peter, 1758; portion of 1 box (Box 7)
  - Livingston, Philip Philip, 1758; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 7)
  - Milner, John, 1758; portion of 1 box (Box 7)
  - Ogden, Isaac, 1758; portion of 1 box (Box 7)
  - Paterson, James, 1758; portion of 1 box (Box 7)
  - Pomeroy, Ralph, 1758; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 7)
  - Shippen, John, 1758; portion of 1 box (Box 7)
  - Smith, Jasper, 1758; portion of 1 box (Box 7)
  - Smith, Thomas, 1758; portion of 1 box (Box 7)
  - Ten Broeck, Dirk, 1758; portion of 1 box (Box 7)
  - Tennent, John Van Brugh, 1758; portion of 1 box (Box 7)
  - Tennent, William Jr., 1758; portion of 1 box (Box 7)
  - Tichenor, Joseph, 1758; portion of 1 box (Box 7)
  - Van Rensselaer, Jeremiah, 1758; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 7)
  - Whitwell, William, 1758; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 7)
  - Williams, Jesse, 1758; portion of 1 box (Box 8)
  - Anderson, James, 1759; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Anderson, James, 1759; portion of 1 box (Box 8)
  - Caldwell, James, 1759; portion of 1 box Contains oversize material. (Box 8)
  - Campfield, Jabez, 1759; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 8)
  - Carmichael, John, 1759; portion of 1 box (Box 8)
  - Clark, John, 1759; portion of 1 box (Box 8)
  - Hunt, James, 1759; portion of 1 box (Box 8)
  - Huntington, John, 1759; portion of 1 box (Box 8)
  - Johnston, Philip, 1759; portion of 1 box (Box 8)
  - Lesly, James, 1759; portion of 1 box (Box 8)
  - Livingston, Walter, 1759; portion of 1 box (Box 8)
  - Lyon, James, 1759; portion of 1 box (Box 8)
  - Nivins, Samuel, 1759; portion of 1 box (Box 8)
  - Noyes, Ebenezer, 1759; portion of 1 box (Box 8)
  - Noyes, Joshua, 1759; portion of 1 box (Box 8)
  - Noyes, Nathaniel, 1759; portion of 1 box (Box 8)
  - Pierce, Thomas, 1759; portion of 1 box (Box 8)
  - Reynolds, Thomas, 1759; portion of 1 box (Box 8)
  - Sherburne, Henry, 1759; portion of 1 box (Box 8)
  - Spencer, Samuel, 1759; portion of 1 box (Box 8)
  - TenBroeck, Dirk, 1759; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Van Buskirk, Jacob, 1759; portion of 1 box (Box 8)
  - Wait, Barnet, 1759; portion of 1 box (Box 8)
  - Alexander, Joseph, 1760; portion of 1 box (Box 9)
  - Archer, John, 1760; portion of 1 box Contains oversize material. (Box 9)
  - Blair, Samuel, Jr., 1760; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 9)
  - Brown(e), W.B., 1760; portion of 1 box (Box 9)
  - Graham, Richard Crouch, 1760; portion of 1 box (Box 9)
  - Green, Enoch, 1760; portion of 1 box (Box 9)
  - Greville, Samuel, 1760; portion of 1 box (Box 9)
  - Greville, Samuel, 1760; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Handy, Isaac, 1760; portion of 1 box Contains oversize material. (Box 9)
  - Huston, Alexander, 1760; portion of 1 box (Box 9)
  - Kelsey, Enos, 1760; portion of 1 box (Box 9)
  - Robbins, Ammi Ruhamah, 1760; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 9)
  - Rush, Benjamin (file 1), 1760; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. Contains oversize material. (Box 9)
  - Rush, Benjamin (file 2), 1760; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. Contains oversize material. (Box 9)
  - Sergeant, Erastus, 1760; portion of 1 box (Box 9)
  - Slemmons, John, 1760; portion of 1 box (Box 9)
  - Smith, Jonathan Bayard, 1760; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 9)
  - Thatcher, Josiah, 1760; portion of 1 box (Box 9)
  - Thompson, Amos, 1760; portion of 1 box (Box 9)
  - Van Harlingen, Johannes (Martinus), 1760; portion of 1 box (Box 9)
  - Wynkoop, Henry, 1760; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 9)
  - Caldwell, David, 1761; portion of 1 box (Box 9)
  - Gillespie, David, 1761; portion of 1 box (Box 10)
  - Handy, Isaac, 1761; portion of 1 box (Box 10)
  - Henderson, Thomas, 1761; portion of 1 box (Box 10)
  - Jauncey, William, 1761; portion of 1 box (Box 10)
  - Ker, Nathan, 1761; portion of 1 box (Box 10)
  - Lefferty, John, 1761; portion of 1 box (Box 10)
  - Lockwood, Samuel, 1761; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - McCracken, Thomas, 1761; portion of 1 box (Box 10)
  - McDowel, Benjamin, 1761; portion of 1 box (Box 10)
  - Oliver, Peter, 1761; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Rice, David Jr., 1761; portion of 1 box (Box 10)
  - Rosbrugh, John, 1761; portion of 1 box (Box 10)
  - Sloan, Samuel, 1761; portion of 1 box Contains oversize material. (Box 10)
  - Thomson, James Hamden, 1761; portion of 1 box (Box 10)
  - Van Derveer, Lawrence, 1761; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 10)
  - Woodbridge, Jahleel, 1761; portion of 1 box (Box 10)
  - Alison, Hugh, 1762; portion of 1 box Contains oversize material. (Box 10)
  - Allen, Isaac, 1762; portion of 1 box (Box 10)
  - Bainbridge, Absalom, 1762; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 10)
  - Davenport, Ebenezer, 1762; portion of 1 box (Box 10)
  - Davis, Edmund, 1762; portion of 1 box (Box 10)
  - Gantt, Edward, 1762; portion of 1 box (Box 10)
  - Harris, John, 1762; portion of 1 box (Box 10)
  - Hazard, Ebenezer, 1762; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 11)
  - Hulbert, John, 1762; portion of 1 box (Box 11)
  - Ludlum, Nehemiah, 1762; portion of 1 box (Box 11)
  - Manning, James, 1762; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. Contains oversize material. (Box 11)
  - Manning, Nathaniel, 1762; portion of 1 box (Box 11)
  - Martin, Thomas, 1762; portion of 1 box (Box 11)
  - McCrea, John, 1762; portion of 1 box (Box 11)
  - Mercer, John, 1762; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Mercier, John Dyer, 1762; portion of 1 box (Box 11)
  - Morrow, ?, 1762; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Morrow, unknown, 1762; portion of 1 box (Box 11)
  - Ogden, Uzal, Jr., 1762; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Peppard, Francis, 1762; portion of 1 box (Box 11)
  - Periam, Joseph, 1762; portion of 1 box (Box 11)
  - Ruston, Thomas, 1762; portion of 1 box (Box 11)
  - Sergeant, Jonathan Dickinson, 1762; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 11)
  - Shepherd, Dickinson, 1762; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 11)
  - Smith, Hezekiah, 1762; portion of 1 box (Box 11)
  - White, Caleb, 1762; portion of 1 box (Box 11)
  - Woolley, Jacob, 1762; portion of 1 box (Box 11)
  - Boyd, James, 1763; portion of 1 box (Box 11)
  - Close, John, 1763; portion of 1 box (Box 12)
  - Cooper, Robert, 1763; portion of 1 box Contains oversize material. (Box 12)
  - Cowell, David, 1763; portion of 1 box (Box 12)
  - Craighead, John, 1763; portion of 1 box (Box 12)
  - Eakin, Samuel, 1763; portion of 1 box (Box 12)
  - Emerson, Ezekiel, 1763; portion of 1 box (Box 12)
  - Hart, Noah, 1763; portion of 1 box (Box 12)
  - Jauncey, James Jr., 1763; portion of 1 box (Box 12)
  - Lathrop, John, 1763; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 12)
  - Lyon, Joseph, 1763; portion of 1 box (Box 12)
  - Noble, Obadiah, 1763; portion of 1 box (Box 12)
  - Paterson, William, 1763; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 12)
  - Pynchon, Nathan, 1763; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Redman, John, 1763; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Reeve, Tapping, 1763; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. Contains oversize material. (Box 12)
  - Simpson, John, 1763; portion of 1 box (Box 12)
  - Tennent, William Mackay, 1763; portion of 1 box (Box 12)
  - Watt, James, 1763; portion of 1 box (Box 12)
  - Williams, Simon, 1763; portion of 1 box (Box 12)
  - Worth, Joseph, 1763; portion of 1 box (Box 12)
  - Alkin, Thomas, 1764; portion of 1 box (Box 12)
  - Claggett, Thomas John, 1764; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 13)
  - Foster, William, 1764; portion of 1 box (Box 13)
  - Hazard, Nathaniel, 1764; portion of 1 box (Box 13)
  - Lawrence, John, 1764; portion of 1 box (Box 13)
  - Leake, Samuel, 1764; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 13)
  - McCrery, John, 1764; portion of 1 box (Box 13)
  - Miller, Alexander, 1764; portion of 1 box (Box 13)
  - Platt, David, 1764; portion of 1 box (Box 13)
  - Smith, Joseph, 1764; portion of 1 box (Box 13)
  - Tredwell, Thomas, 1764; portion of 1 box (Box 13)
  - Tuttle, James, 1764; portion of 1 box (Box 13)
  - Wilson, Andrew, 1764; portion of 1 box (Box 13)
  - Woodhull, William, 1764; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 13)
  - Bacon, John, 1765; portion of 1 box (Box 13)
  - Bay, John, 1765; portion of 1 box (Box 13)
  - Benedict, Joel, 1765; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 13)
  - Chambers, Joseph, 1765; portion of 1 box (Box 13)
  - Corbin, George, 1765; portion of 1 box Contains oversize material. (Box 13)
  - Craven, Gershom, 1765; portion of 1 box (Box 13)
  - Craven, John, 1765; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Craven, Joseph, 1765; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Davies, William, 1765; portion of 1 box (Box 13)
  - Edwards, Jonathan, Jr., 1765; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 14)
  - Finley, Joseph, 1765; portion of 1 box (Box 14)
  - Finley, Samuel, Jr., 1765; portion of 1 box (Box 14)
  - Goodman, Richard, 1765; portion of 1 box (Box 14)
  - Halstead, Robert, 1765; portion of 1 box (Box 14)
  - Hutson, Richard, 1765; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 14)
  - Kirkland, Samuel, 1765; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. Contains oversize material. (Box 14)
  - McCausland, Alexander, 1765; portion of 1 box (Box 14)
  - Mitchel, Alexander, 1765; portion of 1 box (Box 14)
  - Mitchell, Alexander, 1765; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Ogden, Jonathan, 1765; portion of 1 box (Box 14)
  - Ogden, Robert III, 1765; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 14)
  - Parkinson, Henry, 1765; portion of 1 box (Box 14)
  - Pemberton, Ebenezer, 1765; portion of 1 box (Box 14)
  - Pierson, Matthias, 1765; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Pope, Edward, 1765; portion of 1 box (Box 14)
  - Ramsay, David, 1765; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 14)
  - Romeyn, Theodore (Dirck), 1765; portion of 1 box (Box 14)
  - Romeyn, Thomas, 1765; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Rush, Jacob, 1765; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 14)
  - Staples, John, 1765; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 14)
  - Stevenson, Henry, 1765; portion of 1 box (Box 15)
  - Thayer, Alexander, 1765; portion of 1 box (Box 15)
  - Van Arsdale, Jacob, 1765; portion of 1 box (Box 15)
  - Voorhees, Stephen, 1765; portion of 1 box (Box 15)
  - Wheelock, Ralph, 1765; portion of 1 box (Box 15)
  - Williams, Samuel, 1765; portion of 1 box (Box 15)
  - Williams, Simeon, 1765; portion of 1 box (Box 15)
  - Avery, Waightstill, 1766; portion of 1 box (Box 15)
  - Balch, Hezekiah, 1766; portion of 1 box (Box 15)
  - Balch, Hezekiah James, 1766; portion of 1 box (Box 15)
  - Burt, Joseph, 1766; portion of 1 box (Box 15)
  - Chase, Caleb, 1766; portion of 1 box (Box 15)
  - Cheever, Jonathan, 1766; portion of 1 box (Box 15)
  - Clymer, Daniel Cunyngham, 1766; portion of 1 box (Box 15)
  - Cowell, Ebenezer, Jr., 1766; portion of 1 box (Box 15)
  - Edmiston, Samuel, 1766; portion of 1 box (Box 15)
  - Ellsworth, Oliver, 1766; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 15)
  - Haley, John, 1766; portion of 1 box (Box 15)
  - Hasbrouck, Joseph, 1766; portion of 1 box (Box 15)
  - Haslett, Moses, 1766; portion of 1 box (Box 15)
  - Howell, David, 1766; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 15)
  - Jones, Daniel, 1766; portion of 1 box (Box 16)
  - Kellogg, Solomon, 1766; portion of 1 box (Box 16)
  - Lewis, Josiah, 1766; portion of 1 box (Box 16)
  - Livingston, Peter Van Brugh, Jr., 1766; portion of 1 box (Box 16)
  - MacPherson, John, 1766; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 16)
  - Martin, Luther, 1766; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. Contains oversize material. (Box 16)
  - McCalla, Daniel, 1766; portion of 1 box (Box 16)
  - Niles, Nathaniel, 1766; portion of 1 box Contains oversize material. (Box 16)
  - Power, James, 1766; portion of 1 box (Box 16)
  - Skillman, Isaac, 1766; portion of 1 box (Box 16)
  - Smith, Samuel, 1766; portion of 1 box (Box 16)
  - Smith, William, 1766; portion of 1 box (Box 16)
  - Spring, Alpheus, 1766; portion of 1 box (Box 16)
  - Stelle, Benjamin, 1766; portion of 1 box (Box 16)
  - Townsend, Micah, 1766; portion of 1 box (Box 16)
  - Woodhull, John (Trustee), 1766; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 16)
  - Woodman, Joseph, 1766; portion of 1 box (Box 17)
  - Avery, Isaac, 1767; portion of 1 box (Box 17)
  - Barber, Francis, 1767; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 17)
  - Briggs, Zephaniah, 1767; portion of 1 box (Box 17)
  - Cunningham, Samuel, 1767; portion of 1 box (Box 17)
  - Curtis, Francis, 1767; portion of 1 box (Box 17)
  - Devens, Richard, 1767; portion of 1 box (Box 17)
  - Hasbrouck, Jacob I., 1767; portion of 1 box (Box 17)
  - Jones, Elias, 1767; portion of 1 box (Box 17)
  - Morse, Asarelah, 1767; portion of 1 box (Box 17)